
{
    "multiple choice": [
{
    "num":1,
    "question": "In a window, at the top is the _____, immediately below it is the _____.",
    "choices": [
        "(A) Toolbar, Titlebar",
        "(B) Titlebar, Toolbar",
        "(C) Titlebar, Menubar",
        "(D) Menubar, Titlebar"
    ],
    "answer":"(C) Titlebar, Menubar"
},
{
    "num":2,
    "question": "The _____ are a collection of shortcut icons for commonly used functions.",
    "choices": [
        "(A) Text boxes",
        "(B) Toolbars",
        "(C) Tables",
        "(D) Cliparts"
    ],
    "answer":"(B) Toolbars"
},
{
    "num":3,
    "question": "_____ is not a web page editor.",
    "choices": [
        "(A) Adobe Pagemaker",
        "(B) MS Frontpage",
        "(C) Netscape Navigator",
        "(D) Netscape composer"
    ],
    "answer":"(C) Netscape Navigator"
},
{
    "num":4,
    "question": "Which instructs a Web browser on how to format and process a hypertext document?",
    "choices": [
        "(A) Documents",
        "(B) Tags",
        "(C) Elements",
        "(D) Programs"
    ],
    "answer":"(B) Tags"
},
{
    "num":5,
    "question": "Web page editors are _____ application packages.",
    "choices": [
        "(A) Data processing",
        "(B) System",
        "(C) Software",
        "(D) Hardware"
    ],
    "answer":"(C) Software"
},
{
    "num":6,
    "question": "With the help of a word processor we can save our work as",
    "choices": [
        "(A) ASCII text file",
        "(B) Internet",
        "(C) Picture",
        "(D) Image"
    ],
    "answer":"(A) ASCII text file"
},
{
    "num":7,
    "question": "Name the element content to be manipulated by the tags.",
    "choices": [
        "(A) Text between the start tag and end tag",
        "(B) Text before the start tag",
        "(C) Text after the end tag",
        "(D) None of these"
    ],
    "answer":"(A) Text between the start tag and end tag"
},
{
    "num":8,
    "question": "How many font sizes are permitted by HTML to display text?",
    "choices": [
        "(A) 4",
        "(B) 5",
        "(C) 6",
        "(D) 7"
    ],
    "answer":"(D) 7"
},
{
    "num":9,
    "question": "Which of the following specifies the space between the border of the cell and its contents?",
    "choices": [
        "(A) CELLPADDING",
        "(B) CELLSPACING",
        "(C) BORDER",
        "(D) WIDTH"
    ],
    "answer":"(A) CELLPADDING"
},
{
    "num":10,
    "question": "_____ are like the drop down lists used in windows dialog boxes.",
    "choices": [
        "(A) Menu controls",
        "(B) Radio button",
        "(C) Buttons",
        "(D) Password"
    ],
    "answer":"(A) Menu controls"
}

    ]
}

